(忆往昔)
我现在已经难辨真假了
I'm having a difficult time figuring out what's real.
-幻觉吗  -有时我会看见路西法
- Hallucinations? - Sometimes I see Lucifer.
等一下  你不会现在也能看到他吧
Wait, are you seeing him right now?
让我看看你的手
Let me see your hand.
你受伤的时候我跟你在一起
I was with you when you cut it.
我给你缝的针
I sewed it up.
这是真实的
This is real.
在炼狱中有着比那些灵魂更加古老的东西
There are things much older than souls in purgatory,
你当时也一并吞下了
and you gulped those in, too.
-我挡不住他们  -挡住谁
- I can't hold them back! - Hold who back?
利维坦
Leviathan!
那些  不管是什么东西
Those... whatever-you-call-'ems...
利维坦
Leviathan.
如果他们进入了水管
If they're in the pipes,
就像上了高速  四通八达
they got themselves a highway to anywhere.
苏福尔斯综合医院出了食人案了
Something's eating folks down at sioux falls general hospital.
只要我们在适当位置安插好人手
A few of us in the right positions,
每天都将是饕餮盛宴
and we could feast every single day.
我们在我家见面吧  我们重新部署
I'll meet you at the house. We can regroup.
这地方被火烧了
That place was torched.
干这事的人目的明确
Somebody knew what they were doing.
鲍比
Bobby!
不
Oh, no.
两个男性病人  一个有颅脑损伤
I got two males -- one with a head trauma,
另一个胫骨骨折
the other with an open tibia fracture.
我们刚开进苏福尔斯
We're just pulling in to Sioux Falls.
苏福尔斯综合医院吗
Sioux falls general?
你得带我们去别的地方  任何地方
You got to take us somewhere else. Anywhere!
求你了
Please!
也许我不是真实存在的
Hey, so maybe I'm not real,
但我哪里也不去  萨姆
but I'm not going anywhere, Sam.
小萨姆  别离开我  听见了吗
Sammy? You stay with me, you hear?
-他癫痫发作  -小萨姆
- He's seizing. - Sammy!
(如今)
按住他
Hold him down.
三  二  一  好了
Three, two, one, set!
护士
Nurse!
放松点
Just relax.
我现在在哪
Where am I?
你在医院里
You're at the hospital.
-哪一家  -苏福尔斯综合医院
- Which one? - Sioux Falls general.
我弟弟在哪  我们得走了
Where's my brother? We got to go.
他的头部受到严重撞击
He bashed his head quite seriously.
我们带他去做核磁共振了
He's gone up for an MRI.
好吧  我得走了
Okay. I got to go.
伙计  你的腿这个样子你哪也去不了
You're not going anywhere on this leg, buddy.
(苏福尔斯  综合医院)
不  不  不
Oh, no, no, no.
什么情况
What?
你没事吧
You okay?
鲍比  你还活着啊
Bobby, you're alive.
废话  你怎么掉地上了
'Course I am. Why are you on the floor?
他们给我打了吗啡  打了很多
They gave me morphine, a lot.
听着  一个怪物把我腿弄折了
Hey, look, a monster broke my leg.
等等  你的房子
Wait...the house.
我们以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
我没死  至少现在还活着
Well, I ain't. Not yet.
但我们得逃走了
But we got to run.
这地方不安全
This place ain't safe.
萨姆在哪
Where's Sam?
我想可能在做头部扫描吧
Uh... Head scan, I think.
在救护车停靠站等我
Meet me at the ambulance dock, stat.
-我去找萨姆  -等等  在哪
- I'll find Sam. - Wait, where?
鲍比  我现在瘸着呢
Bobby, I'm a gimp.
我想你应该已经安排好咱们的甜点了吧
You've scheduled dessert, I presume?
什么事
Yes?
温彻斯特兄弟吗
The Winchesters?
等一下  小伙子  这是谁
Hold the phone there, son. Who's this?
对  就是这家伙  深度昏迷
Yeah, this is the guy. Coverage lapsed.
我们得送他去郡医院
We're shipping him to county.
快走吧  病秧子
Come on, sicko.
等到了安全的地方再治好你
Let's get you healed up someplace a little safer.
快点  迪恩
Come on, Dean.
妈的
Balls.
快点  迪恩
Come on, Dean.
Come on, Dean!
快走  快走  快走
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
[邪恶力量 第7季第3集]
(蒙大拿州  怀特菲什  三周后)
伙计  快看里卡多
Dude...Ricardo.
发生什么事了
What happened?
自杀了
Suicidio.
永别了
Adios.
这个应该能让你高兴起来
Well, this ought to cheer you up.
我的宝贝
My baby!
只等把这烦人石膏卸掉
Now I just got to get this stupid thing off
我就又能开车了
and I can drive again.
外面情况怎么样
So how is it out there?
很怪很血腥
Weird with a side order of bloody.
我和几个猎人聊了聊
Talked to a few hunters.
他们也遇到了在那家医院开"小吃部"的
They're running into the same kind of thing
那种怪物
that set up shop at that hospital.
还有别忘了我俩差点死在你家
Yeah, and don't forget tried to kill us at your place.
我们一致认为...
Well, consensus is they're, um,
他们就像易形者
they're like shapeshifters
只是更爱吃人肉
only a lot more into eating folk.
而且没有东西能杀了他们
And nothing can kill 'em.
真是好时光啊  还有什么别的吗
Good times. Anything else?
有  他们流出的是黑色的胶状物
Yep. They bleed black goo.
就像从小卡身体里流出的一样
Like that stuff that came out of Cass --
这些从炼狱里跑出来的...
Those things from purgatory.
-叫利维坦  是吧  -对
- Uh...Leviathan. - Yep.
你那警长朋友
What about those chompers
在医院看到的那几个食人族呢
that you and the sheriff saw at the hospital?
他们还在吃人肉汉堡吗
They still making spleenburgers?
没错  打了几个电话
Yeah, made some calls.
那个医生再也没回来上班
That doctor never showed back up to work.
还有一位护士以及几个管理员
Ditto a nurse and some administrators.
-你从未离开  -那么他们可能在
- You never left. - So they could be at
美国的任何一家医院
any hospital in America.
你怎么想  小萨姆
What do you think, Sammy?
小萨姆
Sammy?
萨姆
Sam.
-萨姆  -回家吃饭啦
- Sam... - Hey, ground control!
萨姆
Sam!
怎么了  我...我在这儿呢
Yeah. What? I'm -- I'm right here.
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事
Yeah. I'm fine.
好的
Good.
以前的所有资料都化为灰烬
Every last bit of info I ever had burned down,
-所以...  -这地方呢
- So... - What about this place?
鲁弗斯没留下什么吗
Rufus leave anything?
地下室看过了吗
Did you check the basement?
C型即食军粮和一堆尘土
C-rations and dust.
我想他好几年都没来过这儿了
I don't think he'd been here in years.
好了  我得去重整之前的图书馆了
So, I got to go round up my old library.
我记得你说过那些书大部分都只此一本
I thought you said most of those books were one-of-a-kind.
没错  所以我才在各处藏匿了副本
Yeah. That's why I stashed copies all over the place.
好的
Okay, good. Um...
那位两腿人士  我们没粮食了
Hey, uh, two-legs. We're fresh out of grub.
要不你去买点回来
Want to make a run?
没问题
Sure. Yeah.
温柔待她  好吗
Be careful with her, would you?
萨姆
And, uh, Sam?
怎么了
Yeah?
馅饼
Pie.
还用你说
Obviously.
-所以  -"所以"什么
- So? - "So" What?
你转移话题前
Before you bail again,
那边正上演《移魂女郎》呢
"Girl, Interrupted" over there.
有什么想法吗
Any thoughts?
在我看来他的状态有好转
Looks to me like he's doing better.
好转  你指什么  居然说好转
Better? What do you mean, better?
刚才你不也看见了
You just saw him!
看见他只走神了一次
Saw him check out once.
-可喜的进步  -你开玩笑吧
- That's progress. - You're kidding!
我觉得萨姆的大脑
Look, seems to me that Sam's head
和你的伤腿并无两样
ain't no different than your leg.
伤口愈合总有个过程
People heal on a curve.
并无两...鲍比
Not diff-- Bobby,
五天后我摆脱这玩意儿
I get this thing off in five days,
能完好如初
I'm golden.
萨姆那不叫过程
Sam's not a curve.
他就是个定时炸弹
He's a frickin' time bomb.
他又没在隐瞒什么
It ain't like he's keeping secrets.
眼见为实
What you see is what you get.
称其为进步又有什么好大惊小怪的
What's so nuts about calling it an upswing?
因为这行不通  鲍比  一向如此
Because that's not how it works, Bobby, ever!
好吗  尤其是在萨姆身上
All right? Especially not with Sam.
他早晚会出事
The other shoe is gonna drop.
-就是个早晚的事  -行
- It's just a matter of when. - Okay.
我们还是先考虑眼下的事吧
How 'bout we worry about today's problems?
眼下  我们急需情报
And today, we need intel.
我去找  你坐这儿杞人忧天吧
I'm going. You sit there and stew.
我会打电话来
I'll check in.
听着  你坐在这干着急
Look...You sitting here wringing your hands
也没有任何用处
ain't gonna do nothing.
也许他会让你刮目相看
Maybe he'll surprise you.
(冰锥杀手重现江湖)
报纸也要吗
Paper, too?
是的  来一份
Uh, yeah. Yeah, please.
给
Here.
(莱米·凯尔密斯特)
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
您在账单上还发现了其他的异常款项吗
Do you see any other strange charges on your statement?
比如5月27日的
The May 27th charge to
《玛格达情妇》
"Mistress Magda", perhaps?
抱歉  得罪了
Oh. Sorry for asking.
(交易警告  莱米·凯尔密斯特  蒙大拿州  怀特菲什市)
我们待会再给您打过去
We're gonna have to call you back.
有事吗
Yes?
是的
Yes, sir.
我的监控程序发现了一个温彻斯特兄弟
The Winchesters have triggered one of my search programs.
很好
Great.
蒙大拿州的一家小店
A shop in Montana,
离这儿大概一天半  或许两天的车程
about a day and a half, maybe two days from here.
然后呢
So?
然后
你怎么还在和我通话
So, why are you still talking to me?
-谢谢  -不客气
- Ah, thank you. - Yep.
鲍比去哪了
Where's Bobby?
-他走了  -是的
- He take off? - Yeah.
萨姆  你状态如何
Hey, Sam, how're you doing?
很好
Fine.
你还会...
I mean, you still, you know...
我...我知道你的意思
Yeah, no, I-I know what you mean.
没错  我仍然能看见烂七八糟的幻象
Yeah, I'm -- I'm still seeing crap that's not real.
但我没事
But, yeah, I'm fine.
我能看出真伪
I mean, I can tell the difference.
感觉有好转吗
Think it's getting better?
说实话吗
Honestly? Uh...
其实我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道我应付得来  所以...
I just know I'm managing it, so...
所以不必担心
So don't worry.
馅饼呢
Where's the pie?
我买了蛋糕
I got cake.
差不多了  不是吗
It's close enough, right?
(疑似"冰锥杀手"所害  警方正调查中
死者致命伤口即凶手"标志")
没错  依我之见
Yeah, so, from what I can tell,
应该是妖狐所为
it's something called a Kitsune.
没有很大区别
Not much.
他们...长得像人类...
They...look human...
不过他们会生出利爪
till they sprout out claws
从你耳后刺入以吸食大脑
and stab you behind your ear to get to your brain.
我...我还不知道
I don't -- I don't know yet.
没错  迪恩  我知道杀死他们很重要
Yes, Dean, I realize killing 'em's important.
也许鲍比叔叔能给一本用英语写的书
Maybe if Uncle Bobby sent a book in english.
我有
I am!
不  别...别让他接电话
No, no, don't -- don't put him on the phone.
爸爸
Hi, Dad.
是的
Yes, sir.
我知道死人了
I realize people are dying.
好  我现在就去图书馆
Yeah, I'm on my way to the library right now.
对不起  亲  涨价了
Sorry, honey. Price went up.
55块
$55.
我钱不够
Oh, I don't -- I don't have it.
真可惜
That's too bad.
或许我们可以做个交易
Maybe we can make a little trade.
(过几天就回来  我很好  萨姆)
出事了
Other shoe!
谁出事了
Other who?
萨姆  他走了
Sam. He took off.
去哪儿了
Where?
不知道  不是什么好地方
I don't know. Nowhere good.
或许他只想一个人静静
Well, maybe he needed a little "Me-time."
他可不是一个人在静静
Yeah, but his me-time ain't just him.
就现有情况来看
I mean, for all we know
他可能带着路西法一起上路了呢
he's road trippin' with lucifer somewhere.
留我一个人傻乎乎地呆在这里
Left me here like Jimmy friggin' Stewart.
-我猜你打过他电话了  -语音信箱
- I assume you called. - Straight to voicemail.
他还把GPS给关了
He turned his GPS off, too.
还他开走了我的车
And he took my car!
-淡定  -太晚了
- Don't panic. - Too late!
他说了他没事
Look, he says he's okay,
那就让他呆上几天
so give it a couple of days.
等你拆了石膏
Just till you get the cast off --
再把他抓回来
Then hunt him down.
这几天继续给他打电话就是了
Till then, we'll both just keep calling.
好吧
All right.
你可以退休了
You're goin' down.
你们觉得这又是另一起
You guys thinking this is another one --
冰锥杀手做的案吗
so-called ice pick killer?
同样手法
Same M.O.
不过那家伙死了也好
Can't say I'm too broken up about this one.
你认识他吗
Oh, you knew him?
逮了他不知道多少次了
Busted him half a dozen times.
-大好人啊  -那现在的情况是
- Real mensch. - So, what's the deal?
杀手来镇上  杀几个混混然后走人
Um, killer comes to town, ganks a lowlife, moves along?
差不多
Looks like.
死者的伤口都是一样的是吗  都在耳朵后面
Stabs 'em all exactly the Same, right? Behind the ear?
没错  变态杀人狂
Yeah. No explaining a psycho.
我们没有在报纸上公布细节
We left that detail out of the paper, though.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
我几年前查过类似的案子
I worked a case like this a few years back.
觉得有联系吗
Think it's related?
死者的大脑有没有什么蹊跷
You find anything weird about the brains?
比如
Like what?
大脑丢失
Like...Missing.
去问问验尸官吧
Huh. Good question for the coroner.
好的  谢谢
Right. Thanks.
(三个未接来电)
你好
How you doing?
昨天有没有来过一个大个子
Uh, was there a, uh, big guy in here yesterday?
多了去了
That's specific.
我的意思是
Uh, I mean big.
跟姚明那么高
Like about yea high?
好像有
Maybe.
-棕色头发吗  -是的  就是他
- Uh, brown hair? - Yes, yes. That's him.
你还记得他买了什么吗
Do you, uh -- you remember what he bought?
零食吧
Snacks, maybe?
买没买报纸  还有昨天的报纸吗
How about a paper? Do you have yesterday's paper?
有  那儿
Yeah, right there.
(冰锥杀手重现江湖)
不介意吧
Do you mind?
我们这儿很少有凶杀案
We don't get too many murders out this way...
别说连环杀人了
...much less a serial.
-你们有什么发现吗  -该问我没发现什么
- So what'd you find? - It's what we didn't find.
你看这里
Let me show you.
很大一部分的中脑丢失了
Big chunk of mid-brain went missing.
中脑  脑垂体那块吗
Mid-brain, like pituitary gland?
事实上  他们的脑垂体都被挖走了
Actually, their pituitaries were clear gone.
你是怎么知道的
How'd you know that?
是的  他们需要定期
Yeah, so, they need a steady diet of
吃人类的脑垂体才能生存
human pituitary glands to survive.
推理
Educated guess.
等等  慢点
Hang on. Slow down.
对
Right.
死者都是在离高速不远的停车场被发现的
So, the victims are located in parks just off the highway.
每个镇各一个
Just one per town.
有古怪
That's something.
什么
What?
我累死了
I-I'm just tired.
我看这些资料已经很久了
I've been looking at this for like eight years.
等等
Wait. Hang on.
我马上打回来
I'll call you right back.
一杯焦糖玛奇朵
Triple red eye, please.
好的
Okay.
你的焦糖玛奇朵
Triple red eye.
谢谢
Thanks.
你对着心脏扎下去
You stab it in the heart.
扎心脏
Stab it in the heart.
我说  你刺他的心脏啊
I said, you stab it in the heart!
好了  你们没事了吧
Okay. Are you guys cool?
让我做五分钟正常人可以吗
Can I have a normal life for five minutes now?
迪恩
Oh, Dean.
快问快答
Quick question --
怎么和女生搭讪
How do you talk to girls?
我只是想
I just wanted to, you know,
-跟你问个好  -不
- say hi and... - No.
走开
Go away.
我不能跟男生说话
It's just, I'm not supposed to talk to boys.
走开
Leave me alone.
-得了吧  我们说说话嘛  -我要走了
- Come on. We just want to talk. - I have to go.
怎么这么没礼貌
Why so rude?
别碰我
Don't touch me!
-给我客气点  -为什么你不客气点
-Hey. I said be nice. - Why don't you?
滚开
Butt out.
这小子真找揍
Can you believe this guy?
你好  我叫萨姆
Hi. I'm Sam.
我是艾米
I'm Amy.
见鬼
Oh, damn it.
你好  艾米
Hi, Amy.
萨姆
Sam.
是我
Yeah.
我只是  做梦都没想到会再见到你
I just...never thought I'd see you again.
-你来这里做什么  -你应该清楚啊
- What are you doing here? - I think you know.
你长高了
You got tall, huh?
这会儿还跟我拉家常吗
Small talk? Really?
我们边走边聊
Let's take a walk.
-萨姆  -走啊
- Sam -- - Walk.
同样的手法  同样的猎杀对象
So, Same pattern, same victim pool --
跟我们小时候一样
just like when we were kids.
不  不是这样  听着  我
No, I-it's not what -- look, I'm not --
过去六年我都没换过工作
I've had the same job for the last six years.
我有了房子  养了两只猫  还房贷
I-I have a house, two cats, a mortgage.
我过着正常的生活
I have a normal life.
你管这叫正常
You call this normal?
准备好看医生了吗
Ready to play doctor?
你要不要告诉我
So, you gonna tell me?
说什么
What?
你是怎么打趴那些家伙的
How you kicked the crap out of those guys.
我是说
I mean...
我说了你别生气  你有点...
no offense, but you're kind of...
瘦巴巴的
Wiry?
没错
Exactly.
那么
So...?
我看了很多李小龙的电影
Just watch a lot of Bruce Lee movies.
喝水吗
You thirsty?
好
Sure.
你住在附近
So, you live around here?
不算
No, not really.
歌不错
It's a cool song.
我爸只听1979年
My dad doesn't listen to anything
以前的唱片  所以...
recorded after 1979, so...
所以你也不能听别的
Does that mean you can't?
我很多时候都待在车里
I'm kind of stuck in the car a lot.
我爸总是旅行  因为工作
My dad has to travel. For work.
我妈带着我也是经常漂来漂去
Yeah, me and my mom bounce around a lot, too.
她喜欢那种"让风指引我们的方向吧"
She's all about, like, "Letting the wind be our guide."
嬉皮士那样
Like a hippie?
不包括和平与爱
Minus the peace and love.
我们总是在路上
We're always on the road.
比如世界上最大的麻线团(位于明尼苏达州)吧  我见过两次
I mean, I've seen the world's biggest ball of twine twice.
我见过三次  其实没那么大
Three times. Not that big.
可不是嘛
Right?
好了  老实说
Okay, but be honest --
到处跑的生活没劲透了
I mean, moving all the time sucks.
永远是新来的孩子
You're always the new kid,
而且别人总当你是怪人
and everyone always thinks you're a freak.
萨姆  你就是怪人
Sam, you are a freak.
吉米·亨德里克斯  还有毕加索也是怪人
But so was, I don't know, Jimi Hendrix and...Picasso.
我也是
So am I.
最牛的人都是怪人
All the coolest people are freaks.
萨姆
Sam.
我是什么人  我控制的了
What I am, I'm managing it.
这周你戳死了三个人
You spiked three guys this week.
不  你不明白  不是这样的
No, you don't understand. It's not like that.
我  我不是什么杀人狂
I'm -- I'm not just some murderer.
-只是逼不得已  -为什么
- I had to. - Why?
我不能说
I can't.
我非做不可
I just had to.
请你相信我  萨姆
Please believe me, Sam.
我做不到  对不起
I can't. I'm sorry.
我也一样
So am I.
他要看的就是这个
This is the one he asked to see.
很好
Great, great.
那我问你  他有没有做什么
Uh, let me ask you, did he do anything to it?
没有  他只是问了几个
No. He just asked a few questions
关于其他死者的问题
about the other vics --
缺失的脑垂体等等
Missing pituitary glands and so forth.
该死
Son of a bitch.
萨姆在追查什么
Sam's chasin' a what?
妖狐
A kitsune.
很少见  老爸和我在98年时抓到过一个
It's pretty rare. Dad and I hunted one back in '98.
想不起来了
Vaguely rings a bell.
正常  过程不太精彩嘛
Yeah, didn't make our highlight reel.
好吧  至少我们知道他在忙工作了
Well, least now we know he's working a job.
-但为什么玩消失  -想不出来
- Yeah, but why pull the Houdini act? - Not a clue.
你追到他了要怎么做
What are you gonna do when you catch up?
我自有打算
I got a few ideas.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
你掉了这个
You dropped this.
艾米·庞德
"Amy Pond," Huh?
名字很好听
Cute name.
看来房贷这事儿你没骗人
You weren't kidding about the mortgage.
萨姆
Sam...
等等  那是新鲜的血
Wait, that's fresh.
不是我的
That's not mine.
-你又出手了  -你以为我愿意吗
- So, you killed again! - You think I wanted to?
你到底在做什么  最好告诉我
I think you better tell me exactly what you're doing,
否则不管我愿不愿意都要杀了你
or I have to kill you whether I want to or not!
我不能说
I can't.
-萨姆  你了解我  -我了解过去的你
- Sam, you know me. - No, I knew you.
-那是很久以前了  -不  现在也一样
- That was a long time ago. - No, you know me.
你知道我是什么样的人
You know the kind of person I am.
糟糕
Crap.
对不起  我不是故意的
Sorry. I didn't mean to.
要知道  如果妈妈看到了会发火的
It's just, if she sees it, you know, my mom will be so pissed.
这只是意外
Yeah. It was just an accident.
是啊  可她脾气很大
Yeah, well, she has a temper.
有时候会...没什么
Sometimes. It's...no big deal.
我老爸也一样
My dad does, too.
他喝酒的时候最好躲远点
You don't want to see him when he's drinking.
我妈
My mom...
我觉得她不是个好人
I don't think she's a good person.
有时候我觉得自己也不是好人
Sometimes I don't think I'm a good person, either.
你是好人
You are.
别急着下定论
Don't be so sure.
我见多了坏事
I've been around enough bad
好坏我分得出来
to know good when I see it.
她为我做好了计划
It's just she has this... whole plan for me,
可是  我不想和她一样  明白吗
but...I don't want to be like her, you know?
我也不想变得和我爸一样
I don't want to be like my dad, either.
好吧
All right.
那就告诉我到底怎么回事
So then tell me what's going on.
放下刀子  我就给你看
Drop the knife and I'll show you.
先让我看  我再放下刀子
Show me and I'll drop the knife.
别动
Don't move.
这是雅各布
This is Jacob...
我的儿子
My son.
我在这有了生活  萨姆
I've built a life here, Sam.
还加入了家长教师联谊会  俗人一个
I'm...In the PTA. I'm boring.
-但你还在猎食  -猎食死人
- But you're still feeding. - On the dead.
我做入殓师
I'm a mortician.
我明白
I know.
不算美差  可也有好处
Not sexy, but, you know, health benefits.
我可以悄悄把我和雅各布的每日所需带回来
I quietly take what Jacob and I need.
没有人受伤
No one gets hurt.
可这样风险也很大
But it can be risky,
这样喂食  特别是对一个孩子
feeding like that, especially for a kid.
雅各布病了
Jacob got sick.
他快死了  唯一抗击病魔的办法就是
He was dying, and the only way to fight it off was --
吃新鲜的人脑
He needed fresh meat.
起效了
It worked.
-吃完上一个  他的烧退了  -艾米
- After the last one, his fever broke. - Amy --
-都结束了  -这你无法保证
- It's over. - You can't guarantee that.
我向你保证
I give you my word.
你再杀了我们又有何益处
So, how is spilling more blood gonna help anyone?
你还是可以全身而退
You could still walk away from this.
我们都能
We both can.
萨姆
Sam...
想想我为你做的事
After what I did for you.
-艾米  我  -躲起来
- Amy, I -- - hide!
-怎么了  -快
- What? - Quick!
回来了啊
Hey.
他们追上来了
They caught up.
谁追上来了
Who caught up?
开辆烂英帕拉的两个猎人
Couple of pros in a piece-of-crap Impala.
我们马上走
We're leaving.
妈妈
But, mom --
我就只说一遍
I'm only gonna say this once --
我养家糊口  你就乖乖按我说的做
I put the food on this table, so you will do as you are told
否则就等着饿肚子吧
or I will let you starve.
好吧
Okay.
你去加油  我来收拾东西
Gas up the van. I'll pack.
好孩子
Good girl.
第一次约会还不错吧
Awesome first date, huh?
很抱歉要你这样子离开  可是
Look, I'm sorry you got to go like this, but...
怎么了
What's wrong?
我知道我妈妈
Look, I know my mom's --
没什么  我该走了  抱歉
No, I just have to go. I'm sorry.
那没什么  什么也不是  那是
Oh, that -- that's nothing! That's just...
-萨姆  -英帕拉上的是我爸爸和哥哥
- Sam? - It's my dad and brother in the Impala.
你是个怪物
You're a monster.
你是猎人
You're a hunter.
那
So...
你是要杀了我
You're supposed to kill me...
我也该杀了你吗
and I'm supposed to kill you?
也许吧
I guess.
萨姆  我从没杀过人
Sam, I've never killed anyone.
也不想伤害你
And I don't want to hurt you.
你会伤害我吗
Do you want to hurt me?
不
No.
那还不快走
Then run.
要是我妈发现你  她会杀了你  快跑
If my mom finds you, she'll kill you. Just run.
拜托了  萨姆
Please, Sam.
你好啊  萨姆
Howdy, Sam.
老规矩  不听哥的话就得挨捶
Oh, old rule, you still my baby, you get punched
就这么溜走  你脑子在想什么  萨姆
The hell were you thinking, Sam, running off like that?
据我所知
I mean, for all I know,
撒旦可能又占据你了呢
Satan could have been callin' your plays.
迪恩  我得跟你说多少次  我没事
Dean, look, how many times do I have to tell you? I'm fine.
是啊  没事  你可是心理健康的形象代言人呢
Oh, yeah, no, you're a poster boy for mental health.
你知不知道
You have any idea
我一直在为你担惊受怕  坐立不安
the kind of horror shows I had going on in my head?!
迪恩  我给你留了字条
Dean, I left you a note.
镇上有活儿干
There was a job in town.
一个妖狐
A Kitsune.
是啊  是啊  我知道
Yeah, yeah. Know, I know.
还一直不接我和鲍比的电话  你倒是给个理由
And you ignore Bobby and I's phone calls why, exactly?
因为我想解决好它
Because I wanted to take care of it.
我解决了  都处理好了
And I did. I took care of it.
-是吗  -没错
- Really? - Yes.
尸体在哪儿
Where's the body?
没有尸体
There is no body.
为什么
Why not?
因为我放她走了
Because I let her go.
她走了
She's gone.
什么
You what?
为什么
Why?
萨姆
Sam!
我就知道你藏着东西
I knew you were hiding something.
瞧见没  我们每过一个镇子
See, we can never blow town
艾米都得发发贱
without Amy throwing a bitch-fit.
答应乖乖跟我走了啊
So agreeing to go peacefully -- well.
这是谁
Who is this?
-他是我的朋友  -不  他不是
- He's my friend. - No, he's not.
-萨姆  -闭嘴
- Sam! - Shut up!
你有毛病啊
What is wrong with you, huh?
你真就那么蠢吗
You that stupid? Really?
跟你说过多少次  你不能交朋友
I already told you, you cannot have friends.
这孩子是食物
This kid is food!
不
No!
给你点教训
This'll teach you.
你从没告诉过我
You never told me that.
我谁都没告诉
I never told anyone.
你能想象的出爸爸会怎么做吗
I mean, can you imagine what dad would have done?
你在报纸上看到了那篇报道
So you saw the article in the newspaper,
就匆匆赶来
and you just bolted.
是我留的烂摊子
It was my mess.
你把她放走就算是收拾干净了吗
And you call letting her go cleaning it up?
迪恩  她为了救我杀了她妈妈
She killed her own mom, Dean, to save me.
我知道  萨姆  我知道
I hear you, Sam. I do.
可看看她都做了什么
But look at her now.
她杀了很多人
She's dropping bodies, man...
所以我们就得杀她
which means we got to drop her,
不管她小时候干过多少好事
no matter how many merit badges she racked up when she was a kid.
很抱歉  但事情就这么简单
I'm sorry, but it's that simple.
我们的生活中没有简单的事
Nothing in our lives is simple.
你得跑
You have to run.
艾米
Amy!
你有现钞吗
Do you have cash?
你得赶快坐车离开这里
I-I want you on the first bus out of town.
今晚就走
Tonight.
-那我妈妈...  -我会处理好的
- What about -- - I'll take care of her.
快走吧
Just go!
跟我走吧
Come with me.
我们不必孤单
We don't have to be alone.
我们可以做一对小怪物  萨姆
We can be freaks together, Sam.
萨姆
Sam...
我做不到
I can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我也是
So am I.
听我说  哥懂
Look, man, I get it, okay?
你遇见个姑娘  火花四溅
You meet a girl, you feel that spark --
那是无与伦比的美丽  但她是个怪物
there's nothing better. But this freak?
-我不是那个...  -你就是那个意思
- I didn't mean -- - Yeah, you did.
我注意你看我的眼神了  迪恩
Look, I see the way you look at me, Dean,
好像我是个手榴弹  你就等着我爆炸呢
like I'm a grenade and you're waiting for me to go off.
-萨姆  -我不会爆炸的
- Sam -- - I'm not going off.
或许我是个怪物
Look, I might be a freak,
但这不代表我危险
but that's not the same as dangerous.
-我没说  -没事的
- I didn't say -- - It's okay.
说吧
Say it.
我一直试着变得正常
I've spent a lot of my life trying to be normal,
我这骗谁呢
but come on.
我就是不正常
I'm not normal.
看看我做的那些事
Look at all the crap I've done.
看看我现在  我就是个绝世怪物
Look at me now. I'm a grade-A freak.
但我能控制得了  艾米也一样
But I'm managing it. And so is Amy.
是吗  怎么控制
Is she? How?
她在殡仪馆工作
She works at a damn funeral home
就是为了不用去杀人  迪恩
so she doesn't have to kill anyone, Dean.
她已经找到应对的方法
She's figured out how to deal.
那么那些死人是怎么回事
Okay, well, then explain the bodies.
不是为了她
She's done.
她的孩子要死了  迪恩
Her friggin' kid was dying, Dean.
如果你我是她
Put you or me in her position,
我们大概也会这么做
we'd probably do the same thing.
你不信任她
Look, you don't trust her.
没关系
Fine.
信任我吧
Trust me.
求你了  迪恩
Dean, please.
好吧
Okay.
你当真
Seriously?
早晚得信任你吧
Got to start sometime, right?
波兹曼  没错
Bozeman. Right.
知道了  谢谢
Got it. Thanks.
鲍比的电话  我们今晚在斯波坎市待一宿
That was Bobby. We'll hole up in Spokane tonight.
明天跟他碰面
We'll meet him tomorrow.
你开车吧
Why don't you drive?
你还要揍我吗
You gonna punch me again?
不如你去登记入住吧
Hey, why don't, uh -- why don't you check us in?
我得买点"糖"
I got to hit the candy store.
谨遵医嘱
Doctor's orders.
逃跑的时候  要记着换车牌
Next time you run, you should change your license plates.
不换车牌是很容易被找到的
Keeping the same tags makes you easy to track.
-你是...  -我是萨姆的哥哥
- Who -- - I'm Sam's brother.
你是艾米·庞德
And you are Amy Pond,
波兹曼市失踪的入殓师
the Bozeman mortician who went missing.
有人在找你
There's people looking for you.
萨姆让你来的吗
Sam sent you?
萨姆不知道我来了
Sam doesn't know I'm here.
但他跟你说了吧  我儿子
But he told you. My son --
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
但人...
But people...
是本性难移的
they are who they are.
不管你多努力去改变
No matter how hard you try,
你改不了你的本性
you are what you are.
你还会再杀人的
You will kill again.
我不会的  我保证
I won't. I swear.
相信我  我很清楚
Trust me, I'm an expert.
或许再过一年  或许再过十年
Maybe in a year, maybe 10.
但总有一天你还会杀人
But eventually, the other shoe will drop.
在所难免
It always does.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你能去投奔什么人吗
You got someone you can go to?
你杀过人吗
You ever kill anyone?
如果你杀人了  我会来找你的
Well, if you do, I'll come back for you.
我将来只会杀你
The only person I'm gonna kill is you.
过几年再来找我吧
Well, look me up in a few years.
如果我能活到那天
Assuming I live that long.
没错
Yes, sir.
萨姆·温彻斯特绝对来过这儿
Sam Winchester was definitely here.
是
Yes.
每个我们掌握的他们的假名
Every alias we have for them,
我会查明他们去了哪儿
and I'll find out where they went from here.
他们只比我早走几天
I'm only a couple days behind them.
我先吃顿饭
Just grabbing a bite first.
你知道我发现个什么问题吗
Do you know what I find?
普通的老头子味道还可以
Plain old people taste fine,
但所有的东西...
but everything is better...
蘸芝士都更好吃
with cheese.